I'm finally going to do it.
I'm finally
going to play two time.
I'm level 23 on him. Don't even have
milestone one. So, don't expect the best
gameplay, but it's about time. My hatred
for two time might have to stop. Maybe I
can like drop drop stab.
Oh, that was not it. That was not it.
That was not it. I'm telling you don't
expect the best gameplay. You know, I'm
going to just go for it, bro.
Never mind.
He looks pretty ready for that actually
though.
Oh, nice. Okay. I'll help that guy out.
I'll help that guy out. I'll help that
guy out. Still after that guy. Oh,
that's bad. Oh,
yo, [laughter] that's bad. Yeah, hold
on. I don't want to be seen. I have to
just like follow him and just like make
him afraid.
Oh, that was not it. That was not it.
See, let me
Oh, oh, he baited me with that.
Oh, yeah. This is really bad. If he void
rushes here
Okay, okay. We tricked him. We tricked
him. We tricked him. We tricked him.
That was scary. That was scary. Okay, we
landed one one backstab that game. Let's
go. The next killer is the guest 666.
I don't know how to feel about that cuz
I've heard trick stabbing a guest 666 is
hard cuz of the bigger hit box. Ooh,
this is a really nice like stealthy map
though. I did not mean to
place that there. That's not a I don't
know about that spot. If he if he goes
here
Yes, okay. Oh, shoot. He just like
highlighted me though.
Yeah, that sucks.
Okay, hold on. I've got to get to the
table. Look at the table. Please save
me, table.
Okay.
He might jump over it though. I don't
really
He honestly can. Yo, my obvious or what?
Okay, come on.
Oh, nice. Okay. There we go. Milestone
one. We are pros now. We are officially
pros. Oh, He's right there.
>> [laughter]
>> He's right there.
Wait, this might be a good table spot
actually. This is our new table area.
Right here. Right here. This is perfect.
Kind of.
That doesn't go that far.
>> [laughter]
>> I thought it was a bit farther. Oh, heck
no.
Kind of just going to camp the table
things spot right now. Oh wait, this
guy's here, too.
>> [laughter]
>> Gigi's though. I've got to help Who's
getting chased right now?
Sixter
or a noob?
Okay, I helped them out. Oh, that was
such a good help. I canceled the mass
infection on Icey too. Okay, that is
lit. Which one is he after me now? Oh,
he's after me now. Okay.
I've got to learn how to trickstab fast.
Oh, that's bad. That is bad.
Maybe I should have went for a drop stab
there or something.
That's bad. That's bad. Oh, that's bad.
Okay, how in the world DOES ONE
TRICKSTAB?
I WISH THERE WAS LIKE A TWO TIMES SKIN
WITH a hood. Like
none wear a hood.
I feel like that'd be pretty cool.
Okay, there we go.
And we can still like
Oh, no. Maybe he won't see.
Oh, no, he went that way.
Oh, that was nice. I just like came out
the shadows. Fair. Um
Oh, that was not it. First let's loop
for a second.
Oh, they left. Okay.
Come on. How do I push this?
Right now.
Oh, heck no.
>> [laughter]
>> OH, HECK NO.
NICE. THAT WAS NICE. THAT WAS NICE. You
got him, but that was nice. That was
nice. Did he teleport again? Oh, no, he
did not.
Oh, that was not a backstab.
Oh, yeah. I got to press that earlier. I
got to press that earlier. Okay, so I
think I've just really got to like mash
the stab button. The hit box like
appears a little later than I think I
than I thought it would. He might have
seen me.
Nice.
Oh, matched it too early. Okay.
Or he might have just saw seen me,
honestly. He might have just seen me.
Honestly, I could just like stab him in
the face for my second life though. So,
if worse comes to okay. But if worse
comes to worse, I will just like stab
him in the face cuz
I kind of could just get my second life
right now.
I think that would be safer.
Where's he going?
Screw it.
Oh my god, HE'S OUT OF THE WATER.
OH, THAT DID NOT WORK. I THINK we
if we face stab, we might get a second
life.
Maybe, I don't know.
Oh, they're running out of my stamina.
Oh my god, that was a cheeky dodge.
Yeah, I don't really want to go for a
trick stab unless I'm really like about
to die. It's kind of just going to seal
my fate more.
Oh, heck no.
They did not turn the corner. They did
not turn the corner.
And we're cooked.
Where Where are they going?
No, he he charged [laughter] him out of
my stab.
Okay.
Oh, heck no. I want to have to help this
chance out.
Um Oh, wait, let me DO THIS
THAT WORKS. [laughter] THAT WORKS.
OH MY GOODNESS, I DID not think it'd be
that easy. That looked way harder than
it actually was. Oh goodness, they're
one shot.
Or not one shot. I guess like
Come on.
Okay, that's fine. We distracted them
for the chance.
Okay.
Where's he going to go?
I don't know how I'm going to like
normally trick stab. Then again,
I just need a face stab for a second
life. I don't know how when our luck's
going to run out. You've been dodging
all their projectiles.
What if I just stay still? Woo!
Okay.
I'm going to stay still in the next one,
too. OH, THAT DID NOT WORK.
OKAY, this is looking bad. Looking bad.
I might need the face stab. I might need
the face stab.
Oh, heck no. Yeah, just give me the face
stab. Where are they?
This is so bad. Where are they?
They could just entangle right now.
Okay, wait. Wait.
I need them to like get up close to me.
I need to
Just please.
Okay, we have a second life. We have a
second life. We have a second life.
Oh, no. I was just getting run over
here.
We have our second life. We're chilling.
We're chilling.
Wait, does he not see us?
>> [laughter]
>> He doesn't see us. He doesn't see us. He
doesn't see us.
Oh my goodness.
But I'm not helping this Let's go.
I'm on 11 HP.
You better survive just 20 seconds. No,
there's no way.
Okay, he got us stunned.
Please, it's just 20 seconds. Just live
20 seconds, please.
He How did you die? How did you die? How
did you die? How did you genuinely die?
Okay, we got a little LMS boost.
Dude, how did he die in like 20 seconds?
How is that possible? Hello, 10X.
Oh, no. He cut us off a little there.
Oh, I don't know about looping there.
Oh, shoot. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm
actually dead.
I'm actually so dead. There's no way.
If I live this,
trick stab.
Oh, okay. We I 10 HP though, 10 HP. That
actually is like game saving cuz we can
take another M1.
Dude.
OH,
DUDE, THAT WAS A GOOD GAME THOUGH.
WE ACTUALLY PLAYED really good there.
Dude, I still can't believe that Oh, no.
I still can't believe that Let's
Key. That Let's Key over there died
in 20 seconds.
When I was looping the killer for so
long.
Oh, that was not a backstab.
NO, WHY DID YOU RUN TO THE DISPENSER?
OH, I don't have MY DAGGER. WHAT? I
DON'T HAVE my dagger. Oh, heck no. Okay,
yeah.
Oh, he killed that building man, that's
why.
This is so bad.
Oh, this is so bad. This is way too bad.
Sir, who's Who can I run to right now?
Okay, that's not going to hit me.
There's a two shot Let's Keys.
Two shot Let's Keys, please.
Okay, where are they?
I need to I need to get to them.
Oh, heck no. I got to sneak up on them
somehow.
Nice, okay. I accidentally pulled up the
email wheel with that one too. I was
like you could see how hard I was button
mashing.
Oh, he used blood hook. No way, both of
us [laughter] tried that. Wait, I'm such
a good player, bro.
It's probably going to Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, what the heck?
Wait, I could have stabbed there.
Nice, okay, there we go. Full ablation.
Uh
stab.
Oh, both of us have the same thing.
That's kind of the the most screwed
thing about two time. If there's two two
times
you can just stab him from both
directions and he can't avoid a
backstab. I haven't I haven't thought
about that before. Hold on, let me just
start body blocking for the Elliot.
Okay, nice. I tank for them.
Okay, nice. The tea time helps, too.
Yeah, no, this no strategy is cooked.
Oh, heck no. If he goes up these stairs,
I might be able to do that thing again.
Okay, I don't know about that and saying
IT MAN.
OH, NICE.
There we go. I feel like after that
stab, I deserve to do a generator. I
thought that was like some really hard
tech.
It really isn't.
Oh, there we go team.
Yeah, this guy is kind of just getting
abused.
When we respawn here, I think that
should be good.
No.
Oh, the killer animation.
That sucks. That sucks. I'm so sorry,
Taff. Yeah, now he sees us. I need to
sneak up somehow.
That person just get it like that? Dang.
I'm over here trying to like hide behind
walls and then they just ran up to him.
Nice. Okay. Ronix is probably being a
lot more careful now.
I think I was late.
Oh, he might have turned that way. No.
Okay, it's practically LMS now except
there's two people. We've got to kind of
separate so then we could uh trap for
each other.
Yes, please. Taff. Right here. Right
here, Taff.
Oh, how did he get that?
Oh, heck no, there's a minion here, too.
Wait, I'm kind of This is really bad.
This is really bad.
I just got to live.
Okay. Going here is usually a pretty bad
move cuz of the false loneliness, but
there's like 20 seconds left.
Okay, nice.
Oh, heck no, there's a minion.
Oh, he killed it. Okay.
It's kind of better for us.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. This Taff
Taff Taff Taff, please. Taff Taff. Taff
Taff. Yes.
LET'S GO.
OH, NOT the fridge.
Ah, heck no. Because here
Wait, what? Oh, they were starting
immune at the time. Oh.
Oh my goodness. Okay. Please bring me to
the table. Yes.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. This is how you win
against six here.
I'm right here.
Nice.
Oh, a John Doe.
I There's no way I haven't gone against
a John Doe once in this entire video
until now.
That's really worrying.
Oh, no. I did not mean to hit them like
that.
Yeah, I'm sorry, this guy. I'm so sorry.
Wait, I can drop stab. I can drop stab.
Oh, no, I can't.
Oh, never mind. Oh, he probably can.
Oh, got a little backstab there, too.
Was that worth it? Oh, it was worth it.
It was worth it. It was worth it.
Okay, how are they going to spike?
Can I use this as a No, but I can use
this. There's a tripwire over here, so
it might be worth it, too. Now, they're
going to spike me in.
Okay.
I might start needing help from the
guests though, you know.
Just might. How do I get back up there?
Oh, I can't get back up there.
Kind of forgot about that.
I got to slip past the thing.
Okay, nice.
Okay, I guess the guests cannot help us,
it looks like.
Oh, that's so bad. That's so bad.
Oh,
HOW DID THAT HAPPEN?
OH, MY SECOND LIFE.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME I'VE LIKE
RESPAWNED.
OH, they saw us. Oh, okay. Wait, I might
be able to stab here.
Nice.
I was like in the shadows, too. That was
a good That was a good stealthy stab.
Yeah, that does not work.
>> [laughter]
>> That does not work.
I keep I keep trying to do that like
dash that dash stab tech. I think I'm
going to
not high enough level for that.
I'm just like follow the back of them
right now to be Oh, never mind. Never
mind. Never mind. Never mind. I don't
want to do that. I don't want to do that
actually. I don't want to do that.
You got like hit in the crossfire. Oh,
this is not great.
Okay.
Swift dodge.
Thank you, guest. Oh, that box saved me.
I would have been dead.
I'm not dead. Almost. Oh, W shed stone.
W shed stone.
Oh, no.
Please don't. Oh, no. I'm dead. I'm
dead. I'm dead. Oh, it's another John
Doe.
Okay.
Ritual here. I don't know. He might
footprint this.
Hopefully not.
Okay. Not a backstab. Got a stab though.
Oh, no. They saw me.
Wait.
Oh, I found a pen.
I'm about to get killed, aren't I?
Yeah, no. I'm about to get I'm
[laughter] about to die.
Oh, This is bad. I'm about to get
cornered.
OH, I'M STILL TRAPPED. I'm still
trapped.
Okay, they don't have footprints set up
here. It's nice.
Oh, they do have one here though.
I didn't see that until it was too late.
Okay, hold on. I've got to try to help
them.
No way, all three of us here?
Hell no, hell no, hell no, hell no, hell
no, I'm not trying that.
Okay, nice. The guy got exploded.
Both three two times.
How should I Oh, someone got the trick
stab here.
Okay, [laughter]
that person is getting trick stabbed
after trick stab.
I am not that guy. I am not that guy. I
am not that guy. I saw him eating trick
stab and I was like, that looks easy. It
was not easy.
Oh my goodness, he just got trick
stabbed again. Good, I'm going to join
them and try to do that. Oh, he saw me.
Where's he going?
Oh, they did another trick Oh my god, he
reset. [laughter] Damn. Wait, I might be
able to sneak around here.
All right, nice.
Oh, barely did it. The guy even tried to
charge them into it, too. That was cool.
Nice. I might be able to just camp these
stairs and do a little
this stab. They did not keep going this
way.
Just walked into my back stab, okay?
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
He's still hidden.
He can't see me.
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, I did not flick hard enough like on
the thing.
Heck no.
Oh, I didn't Okay, now he's just raging
face.
Oh, I'm I'm cooked. I'm so cooked.
I've got to loop back to them.
Oh, okay.
Wait, I can just like
run.
And then hide.
In case.
Yeah, now we're good. We're good.
Okay, I think this is going to be my
last game against the John Doe is kind
of worrying and there's only three
people. Okay, that's really worrying.
But now we kind of cooked up.
That takes one spike.
Okay, I took a dodge.
I use shield, too.
Oh, they're after the deuce cars. I just
realized there's two deuce cars and me.
Okay, W W double zap. Wow, holy cow.
Oh goodness.
Not after the deuce car.
Die. That's the end of the video.
Two times actually
I'm not going to say anything. Peace
out. Have a good